https://campbournedale.com/about-the-camp/privacy-policy/

Our Privacy Policy
Camp Bournedale collects personal information such as the camper’s name, postal address, e-mail address, and telephone number, gender, age, and personal interests, credit card information, the type of services or products ordered or purchased, and the date of the order or purchase.
Camp Bournedale will not share your e-mail address with any third parties.
Camp Bournedale may use a camper’s information for “Operational Uses” such as to complete transactions requested by a Camper’s parent or to send administrative communications about a camper’s account.
Camp Bournedale will disclose personal information when it believes in good faith that such disclosures (a) are required by law, including to comply with a court order or subpoena, or (b) will help to: enforce its Terms of Use; protect a camper’s safety or security; and/or, protect the safety and security of its Web sites, Camp Bournedale, and/or third parties.
Additionally, Camp Bournedale will not collect, use or disclose a Camper’s personal information for any other purpose than those identified above, except with the camper’s parent’s consent. We will protect the camper’s personal information with appropriate security safeguards and take appropriate steps to protect the confidentiality of the camper’s personal information. We strive to keep our camper’s personal information as accurate and up-to-date as is necessary for the purposes identified above.
This privacy policy may change without notice to present or past guests. If you have any questions regarding this policy, please contact Darin Fabrizio.
